<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on Bravo LT | Learning &amp; Technology</title>
    <link>http://localhost:8080/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Bravo LT | Learning &amp; Technology</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2018 18:23:33 +0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://localhost:8080/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Pistons vs Cavs</title>
      <link>http://localhost:8080/blog/pistons-vs-cavs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 12:11:29 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/blog/pistons-vs-cavs/</guid>
      <description>Friday Night Road Trip! A few of us from #TeamBravo headed south on Friday night, to the Breslin Center at MSU, to see the Pistons and Cavs face off! Since they&amp;rsquo;ve both lived in Ohio, Ben and Matthew are die-hard Cleveland fans. Ed and Tom cheered for the Pistons which made for a night of light-hearted rivalry between our cheering section of four.
Not only do all of us enjoy working together as a collaborative and united team &amp;ndash; we have a heck of a lot of fun outside the office.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Raspberry Pi Youth Computer Programming Camp is Back!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:8080/blog/raspberry-pi-computer-programming-camp-is-back-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2018 12:11:29 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/blog/raspberry-pi-computer-programming-camp-is-back-2018/</guid>
      <description>At Bravo LT, we believe STEM education is key to strengthening West Michigan from the inside out. We’re excited to host another session of Raspberry Pi Youth Camp, this fall, which will give local students (ages 12-15) an opportunity to explore computer programming in a fun and engaging way.
The free event will be held on September 11 &amp;amp; 12, 2018 at Calvin College in Grand Rapids from 5pm – 8pm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Agile Training in Grand Rapids</title>
      <link>http://localhost:8080/blog/agile-in-grand-rapids/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jul 2018 12:11:29 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/blog/agile-in-grand-rapids/</guid>
      <description>Equip Your Teams with Agile We&amp;rsquo;re passionate about equipping your teams with the cutting-edge Lean Agile Certification training they need!
This summer we hosted an Agile Advanced Scrum Master Certification course in down-town Grand Rapids. We had a blast hosting and teaching participants from Gordon Food Service, Meijer, Spectrum Health, and more. Most beneficially, great discussions formed across the varying industries which created a learning environment filled with collaboration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google I/O Extended</title>
      <link>http://localhost:8080/blog/google-io-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 12:11:29 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/blog/google-io-2018/</guid>
      <description>#BravoDoesIO This summer&amp;rsquo;s Google I/O Extended was held at the Knickerbocker in Grand Rapids. Bravo LT was excited to participate as a Gold Sponsor and host several talks as well as the Game of Drones Code Challenge.
Google brought a lot to the table through their livestream event. Many were amazed to see the Google Assistant make a phone call to book a restaurant on behalf of the user. Google was also quite focused on #DigitalWellbeing so everyone can enjoy technology that improves life and doesn’t distract from it, which seems like an important initiative.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2017 Raspberry Pi Youth Computer Camp Recap</title>
      <link>http://localhost:8080/blog/2017-raspberry-pi-youth-camp-recap/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2017 12:11:29 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/blog/2017-raspberry-pi-youth-camp-recap/</guid>
      <description>At Bravo LT, we believe STEM (Science, Technology, Engineering, Math) education is key to strengthening the future for the next generation. As a technology and e-Learning company in West Michigan, we love introducing the next generation of children to technology. Last month we hosted our third-annual Raspberry Pi Youth Camp which gave local students (ages 10-14) an opportunity to explore computer programming in a fun and engaging way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google IO Extended Code Art Prize</title>
      <link>http://localhost:8080/blog/google-io-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 12:11:29 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/blog/google-io-2016/</guid>
      <description>Code Art Prize Google I/O Extended GR Gold Sponsor Bravo LT is excited to announce Code-Art Prize, our Code Challenge, just in time for this year’s big event! Code-Art Prize is a contest with an emphasis on functional code that is, also, beautiful. The problems will be posted on GitHub Tuesday, May 17, and the Challenge closes Wednesday, May 18, at 3pm. Participants who design the most elegant code will be entered into a raffle to win a Google Home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Go Local</title>
      <link>http://localhost:8080/blog/go-local/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2017 12:11:29 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/blog/go-local/</guid>
      <description>We like supporting local businesses—after all, it creates new jobs, encourages innovation, and strengthens our community. The truth is, though, that’s not the main reason we’re so committed to anything and everything local. Really, we’re just in love with what West Michigan has to offer—the unique people and products that populate every corner of the region.
Bursting with amazing talent, innovation, and services, our area has an answer to every business need, craving, or wish list.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Giving Back - Why Bravo Cares</title>
      <link>http://localhost:8080/blog/why-bravo-cares/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2017 12:11:29 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/blog/why-bravo-cares/</guid>
      <description>When I first interviewed for my position at Bravo LT a little more than a year ago, my interviewer—Bravo LT president Ed—asked me what some of my hobbies were. “Well, I really like listening to music…I like drawing…oh, and I volunteer at the local animal shelter,” I responded. Ed briefly commended me on my volunteering efforts—a nicety, I assumed—and the conversation moved right along.
Fast forward to a few days later when I received an email from Ed telling me I was a good fit for the gig—cool!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy New Year</title>
      <link>http://localhost:8080/blog/happy-new-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2016 12:11:29 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/blog/happy-new-year/</guid>
      <description>2016 was a big year for Bravo LT—a year of profound growth. That growth was demonstrated not only through several valuable new business partnerships, but also through the personal development of our employees. Whether they were brushing up on their professional and team-building skills or volunteering their time to support local causes, our team members showed a willingness and commitment to grow as individuals.
Over the course of the year, Bravo LT grew by two project managers, two e-learning experts, and four exciting new partnerships with organizations across Michigan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Responsive e-Learning - One Size Does Not Fit All</title>
      <link>http://localhost:8080/blog/responsive-e-learning-one-size-does-not-fit-all/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2016 12:11:29 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/blog/responsive-e-learning-one-size-does-not-fit-all/</guid>
      <description>e-Learning modules have traditionally been static—stiff, heavy courses that are not quite optimized for modern-day mobile devices. Designed in a constrained aspect ratio, these modules can technically fit on any size screen, but they are certainly not optimized to fit well—and that’s hardly the best option when you need to train employees on the go, or simply need to train them on a device other than a desktop computer or laptop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bravo LT&#39;s Four Pillars</title>
      <link>http://localhost:8080/blog/bravos-pillars/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2016 12:11:29 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/blog/bravos-pillars/</guid>
      <description>Doing Things Differently We’ve worked hard to earn our reputation as an elite learning and technology solutions provider in the growing West Michigan tech scene. How? We like to do things differently. From the way we invest in our employees, to the strong relationships we foster with clients, we empower the community in all that we do.
Below are the Four Pillars with which we’ve built our foundation. We’ve leveraged our extensive industry knowledge and innovative practices to establish trust with our partners and create synergy within their businesses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How I Spent My Summer Vacation</title>
      <link>http://localhost:8080/blog/how-i-spent-my-summer-vacation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2016 12:11:29 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/blog/how-i-spent-my-summer-vacation/</guid>
      <description>In the contracting world, it’s pretty common for client work to slow down in the warmer months. Summertime is a welcome reprieve from the brutally cold Michigan winters, so I don’t exactly blame clients for wanting to enjoy a little time outside of the office! In fact, as a self-proclaimed beach bum, I, too, find myself distracted by a hot and sunny day when Lake Michigan is above 70 degrees.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bravo LT Hosts Raspberry Pi Camp</title>
      <link>http://localhost:8080/blog/2016-raspberry-pi-youth-camp-recap/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2016 12:11:29 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/blog/2016-raspberry-pi-youth-camp-recap/</guid>
      <description>At Bravo LT, we believe STEM education is key to strengthening West Michigan from the inside out. That’s why we were pleased to host our second-annual free Raspberry Pi Youth Camp which gave local students an opportunity to explore computer programming in a fun and engaging way.
The free event, held August 9 and 11, 2016 at Davenport University in Grand Rapids, was powered by our developers, who generously volunteered their time to teach camp participants about the Python programming language and Raspberry Pi devices—inexpensive credit card-sized computers that plug into TVs or monitors and use keyboards and mice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Importance of Outsourcing Locally</title>
      <link>http://localhost:8080/blog/going-local/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2016 12:11:29 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/blog/going-local/</guid>
      <description>Going Local We all know businesses can outsource cheap work overseas in exchange for second-rate results. But Bravo LT wants your company, and our shared community, to thrive. That’s why we are so passionate about delivering exceptional services to businesses in the area. We believe that investing in your community is the best way to ensure a bright future for West Michigan. Here are just a few of the many reasons why we think it’s so important to outsource locally:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bravo Open Source Symposium</title>
      <link>http://localhost:8080/blog/bravo-open-source-symposium/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2015 12:11:29 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:8080/blog/bravo-open-source-symposium/</guid>
      <description>Bravo Open Source Symposium October 26, November 2, 9, and 16 5:00 - 7:00 PM
Event Description: BOSS 2015 explores specific open source topics, to include:
 Data Grids: To Infinispan and Beyond (Day 1) Introduction to Docker (Day 2) Maven for Power Users (Day 3) Introduction to Clojure (Day 4)  
This free four-day symposium, held on alternating Mondays in September and October, features highly interactive training sessions to include the following delivery methods: traditional lecture and demonstration, video, case studies, hands-on activities and group discussion.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>